<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Research Journey</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/my-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/my-research/</guid>
      <description>What the fish sees in between trials
 How it Started I came to UT Austin with a very murky idea of what I wanted to do in life, only a love for biology and a passion for environmenatl issues.
The best thing I ever did for myself was apply to the FRI (Freshman Research Initiative) the summer before my first semester. Joining the Fish Behavior stream and participating in real research with a lab on campus changed the course of my life-- for the better, of course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, It&#39;s Me!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/hello-it-s-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/hello-it-s-me/</guid>
      <description>Hello, it&#39;s me: Elena! I am a third year biology student at UT Austin studying ecology, evolution, and animal behavior, with a certificate in applied statistical modeling. I am interested in nearly every aspect of biology, but my true passion is for ecology, specifically urban ecology.
I am a researcher, a homebody, a plant collector, and an aspiring animal sanctuary owner (ok maybe not but one can dream, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Stuff!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/python-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/python-stuff/</guid>
      <description>So.. Coding, Huh. Coding is hard. Truly, it is. However! Learning how to program, even just the basics, is an essential tool for many (all?) in today&#39;s technologically saturated world. For researchers and scientists of any capacity it is an incredibly necessary and useful tool to explore, manipulate, and make sense of your data. It&#39;s not so scary; here&#39;s a simple Python code chunk:
print(&amp;quot;When the robots take over, we&amp;#39;ll have to learn their language!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
